Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
The morning chime has rung. We are.
This is SISTAR Executive Director Chugaku.
I, Mayama, will be your facilitator today.
I look forward to working with you.
All right. Keep it up.
Well then, I've already introduced myself, so please introduce yourselves too.
I am Ayaka Yasumoto.
I'm Misie Hoshida.
Please introduce yourselves.
It's been a long time since I've been in the showroom.
It's been 11 months.
11 months?
I see.
I've been here since July, so it's been 9 or 10 months.
It's been 9 months.
How about you, Aya?
It's been six months or so.
About a month?
It's been a long time.
Let's start the showroom as usual, shall we?
Let's start as usual.
Thank you very much for watching the 55th show of EBICHU's Delightful and Fufufuna Showroom today.
This show is the sister show of our showroom, Ukka's showroom.
It's been too long.
It's been too long since I've been here, and we have microphones and studio equipment.
Yes, yes. It's a little cloudy.
I was surprised.
They even hit me on the hip.
I like this one. I'll come back next time.
I just shook my head and the air was clean.
I got soaked.
It's amazing, isn't it?
What else? Anything else that'll make you numb?
We'll definitely do it again next time.
We were in a meeting earlier, and they want to do a taco parade next time or the time after that.
I heard you can do that, so we'll do that.
We have a sense of reason.
We have rational vision. We have all kinds of things.
I'm appealing, right?
We also have the magic of notes.
There are not only fake books, but also proper books.
There are Gosar's books, too.
There are even books about Gothar Yoshida and Gorden Yoshida.
My sisters have been talking to me for a long time.
We always wanted to come. We all wanted to come.
I always wanted to come.
I made this mysterious icon of a shrimp.
A shrimp.
I haven't seen this in a long time.
Oh, I see.
A little fear is also a group of this picture like the same.
Cute surrealistic pictures of ordinary people.
Thank you very much.
This original avatar is.
Please register with SHOWROOM.
You can either pay for it or get it for free.
You can get it by gifting it to us either way.
So, if you haven't changed your avatar yet, please do so.
If you haven't changed your clothes yet, please do so.
Please do so.
It's amazing, isn't it? It looks like a mass. It's like a mass.
I do a little bit of showroom work, so I've seen some of the individuals.
It's been a while.
It's true, it's been a while since I've watched a showroom.
Ko-chan, you need to change. I'll start with the one where you're eating penguin ramen.
Get changed.
And Kikyusuke, the Virgo, next to him.
I wanted to say something too.
And, um... well, this... this... this... this...
This Nogizaka-san.
He's so cute. I knew it. They are so cute when it comes to Nogizaka-san.
We're just as cute as them, so please let them do it.
We're doing it with a mysterious cuteness.
I've done it.
Oh, really?
Did you do it in a cute way?
Did you do it?
I liked it.
It was?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're illustrating something so cute?
It wasn't on the list.
Because it was an illustration, I didn't know about this kind of system where you can make a combination.
Can you make something like this for your personal showroom?
You can see it, right?
Really?
They won't do it.
Hey, can you watch it and do a pen talk with me?
Oh, really?
You can't make it?
But we'll stand out like this.
That's right, that's right. Our picture of Kobayashi is not meant to disrespect him.Yes, yes, yes. I'm not dissing Kobayashi's drawings.
I'm just saying that the cuteness is a little different, that it's a different genre.
I knew it.
Oh, isn't that the one of Char Sweater? This one.
Oh... Oh...
Aren't you afraid of it?
I'm not.
It's cute.
Peach shrimp.
But ours stand out everywhere we go.
That's true.
Rinchu-san's abuta stands out when idols on SHOWROOM come to meet us for a chat.
That's true. You have an unforgettable face.
Well, is that good?
Yes, I think so. She's cute, isn't she?
We're not making any progress.
It's true.
But it's been a while since the three of us have talked together, so I was looking forward to it.
In the beginning, we would have a review meeting with the principal after the show, and we would chat about the show in an attempt to make it more like a TV show, right?
That's right. It started out a bit formal, didn't it? Originally, yes.
You did it in the style of a seetsudo, right?
That's right.
We did it in a seetsu kite, didn't we?
What's with that?
It's like a reward. Thank you very much.
And if you click on the Twitter symbol at the bottom of the screen, you can spread the word about this broadcast on your Twitt er.
So here is the time to spread the word. I'm going to tweet a notice on Twitter now so that many people can see this broadcast.
What are you going to do? Pause.
What do you want to pose?
What pose would you like?
Pose wanted.
Pause wanted.
I want a pose.
I want to do a lot of eye candy.
I'm just too free.
What would be good?
Kimoto-chan and the others are still very formal.
That's true.
They say they're nervous. All the time.
The years of distance between us are different.
They say it's the avatar pose.
This is it.
This is it?
Let's do it this way.
What do you sound like?
He mediocre.
With a face.
Yay.
I'd love to hear from you.
I'm going to ask you to tweet about it now, so please tweet about it.
So, I am sending this to you in a relaxed manner, but I would like to come to a project.
I'm going to call it a fun and funny survey talk.
This is the first time I'm doing this.
We're doing this for the first time. We are.
I might have done it.
You did?
I did it with Moriko.
We did.
I might have done it.
That was six months ago.
It was six months ago.
Aya has a short memory.
That's right.
Aya's memory is a little weak.
She's almost forgotten. She can only remember for about six months. Aya-chan's memory.
Before giving a talk, they take a questionnaire to decide what to talk about. That is called a questionnaire talk.
Yes, I know. Here is today's topic.
Jabekkoron.
(1) A large number of
(2) For how long?
(3) Reunion after more than ten years
(4) A day off
(5) Mamidoshiki
(6) Little Oni
7) Majigachi Free Talk
What is "Majigachi Free Talk"? I wonder.
What does it mean?
Is it by voting?
Yes. I would like to ask you to vote on which of these seven topics you would like to talk about.
There is no such thing as an event in Ebichu. Oh, you are going to write something like that?
What? Did I just write that?
There is no eventful headline.
What? It's about the event, isn't it?
But I've heard that a lot in the other ones, so isn't it good? I've heard that a lot in the other ones.
There's no "Memories of the Music and Performing Arts Festival" or anything like that.
There is no such thing.
That's a lot of things.
If there are two or three upcoming events, we don't know because we haven't been here for a while.
You can read about it in various interviews, so please take a look here.
On the other hand, we are new to this.
Then, let's start the voting!
Please vote.
I miss this.
No hints, too many hints. We're writing this with no hints, too.
That's right.
That's right. We're doing what we want to talk about.
We came to this title that we want to talk about.
So we were told to come prepared with a free talk title.
That's exactly what I did.We did exactly that.
Because the president didn't tell us to do it, we did.
That's right, because the president didn't tell us to.
The president didn't tell us to do it.
Congratulations.
That's amazing.
It's really great.
Congratulations.
It's wonderful.
It always comes up on Twitter.
Well, that's it!
Okay.
So, what were the results of the voting?
Well, let's see.
Number 3.
Reunion after more than 10 years was chosen.
Who gave you this talk theme?
Yes, Aimi.
Aimi.
Yes.
What does this mean?
We met again for the first time in more than 10 years.
And who did I meet again?
I was reunited with a relative of mine, Hane Tokuko.
And to my surprise, the thing that triggered the reunion was Moruku, which I have recently become addicted to.
There it is!
This is the first time for me to meet MORQUE, isn't it?
We met again at MORQUE.
We are about the same age, so we are Hane Tokuko.
So we used to hang out a lot when we were little.
But we didn't see each other for a long time because our lives changed when we started going to school.
I guess they came to see our live performances at each occasion, but we didn't talk.
But we didn't talk.
And then, Haneyoko contacted my mom.
She saw my Instagram.
I had posted a video of her doing Moruku on my Instagram.
She said she saw it.
She said, "I'm doing it, so if you want, let's do it together sometime.
It was a good idea.
We became friends.
So I got in touch with her through her mother.
She's a feather girl, you know.
And we met again.
Oh!
You mean you did Morc together?
Yes, we did Morc together.
But it was kind of a performance group.
First of all, I have to admit, I know her face from her Instagram.
But to be honest, I don't know what he looks like if I haven't seen him for 10 years.
To be honest, I don't know what Hatoko looks like.
You've met her, right?
That's why he was wearing yellow, so that he would stand out.
So that I'd be easy to recognize.
He was wearing a yellow jacket, so it would be easy to recognize.
It's not pink.
It wasn't a pink jacket.
I was going to wear a color that wouldn't be sunny.
But I think he was looking at me, so he noticed right away.
I was like, "Oh, my God.
But I didn't even know what to call you.
Oh, right.
That's the bottom line.
That was when you were a little kid.
But then...
Suddenly it was like, "Let's start from the beginning.
With Hatoko's friends.
It's like the Mork group we always do with Hatoko's friends.
I see.
Hatoko asked me to join her.
Like a morc team.
They put me in the morc team.
And I'm going to do it as a gupa.
And it seems like they participate in tournaments and stuff like that.
And they taught me how to throw and stuff.
He taught me how to throw, and I came back a lot better.
That's a great story!
That's right.
What's Mork?
I don't even know what it is
Morita san does it.
Morita san of Saraba Seishun no Hikari...
There are 12 trees.
Each tree has a score on it.
And the score is 50 points.
If you knock down one of the trees...
If you knock down one of the numbers, that number is your score.
But if you knock down two or more
the number of points will be the number of knocked down numbers.
That's the rule.
20 for 1
The first player to score 50 points wins.
But you have to score 50 points.
If you get out of 50 points...
the score goes back to minus 25 points.
And if you miss twice, you get zero points.
That's why the other team and
If you guess what team you're going to throw to next...
I'll get a point and the score will go up.
So we would do all kinds of calculations.
It's a lot of fun.It's pretty funny.
Not just for the body.
It's a cross between bowling and darts.
As a kind of image
It looks surprisingly difficult.
It looks like I'm just throwing a tree.
I'm going to go up by 11 points.
I'd like to knock down the 7 trees over there.
I'd like to take them down once over here.
It takes a lot of thinking.
You know, trying to get in the way and stuff like that.
Interrupt them.
You do that.
It's a lot of fun.
Did you fight with Hatoko?
Hatoko and I were on different teams the whole time.
Who won?
I thought they were relatives, but they were fighting Hatoko the whole time.
Hatoko was so good.
She was really good.
The way she threw and everything.
She'd say, "I'm going to do the Morita throw.
And Morita threw it the way Morita threw it.
I was so surprised at how good she was.
Now she's Princess Mork!
Mork is so much fun!
I didn't know there were so many people doing it!
Yes, there are a lot of Ebichu family members who do it.
That's amazing!
Where do you meet people?
It's not a word I've ever come across before.
I wonder how they know it.
When we do it in the park, there are even grandmothers.
They're like, "What? And they're like, "What?
I did it with my grandma the other day.
I didn't know that parks could be so open to people.
Anyone can do it.
You don't have to be strong.
All you have to do is throw the tree well.
You can do it with your grandma.
I played against her the other day.
That's great.
I'd like to start, too.
Maybe we could meet at the park.
I guess that's what you mean.
I only see gateball, like Mr. Miura.
I think it's the same feeling as gateball.
It's really...
Sounds like fun.
Surprisingly, I'm in the MOLC club.
The tournaments are held on Saturdays and Sundays, so I often can't participate because of live concerts.
It's my dream to organize a tournament someday.
I'd like to have them create an idol morc club.
I think it's great.
I'm sure you'll be able to pick the same one, but please vote again, and you can pick the same topic.
The president says it's "hmmmmm"... but really... there might be another reunion after more than 10 years...
There might be another reunion after more than 10 years. I'll think about it!
That's a great system, isn't it? I don't know... I've been told nothing, and now I'm being pushed around.
I don't know what's up with the survey auction.
I'd like to try Mork.
Let's do it, let's do it, let's do it.
Let's do it! Here are the results of the voting.
Oh, it's changed. Number 6!
So, who wrote number 6?
Yes! That's enough!
Are we interrupting something? I like the pull.
It's okay, it's a good headline.
You're good. A genius at headlines.
I'm so happy... after all that thought.
We both thought of it in less than a minute.
What's this then?
I'm fighting a little demon.
What do you mean?
What do you mean? It's a little demon on the bottom, about half the size of the tip of your pinky toenail.
It's a tiny little sore on the bottom tip of my lower lip, about the size of half a pinky toenail.
A five-millimeter sore.
We were shooting a music video yesterday.
It was bothering me so much that I chewed on it a little bit at a time.
And today I woke up in the morning a little bit.
That's a silly story.
How do I give him endocoronitis?
I've never had one and I'm fine with it.
You're healthy, right? I'm extremely healthy.
That's what endophthalmitis looks like.
Endophthalmitis... that's it.
It's a white bump.
But they're tiny.
The inside is kind of gouged out and white.
Like a bull's-eye.
It's hyper-itchy.
Yes, it's hyper-itchy.
I also had endophthalmitis last week.
Last week?
The day before yesterday, it got smaller and less painful.
Now they're just gone.
Why?
It's on the underside.
It's so small.
You know, like a pimple, when it's that small.You know, like a pimple... if it's small enough...
If it's a small pimple, you can just squash it or something.
I can give you some medicine or something.
But you can't really do that, can you?
I can't!
How do you do it? I can't do much.
Me neither.
As soon as I get one, I take a nutritional drink or something.
And take something for endometriosis.
Where do you get them?
Everywhere.
But it depends on the person.
Like acne, endophthalmitis.
Don't you get them in the same place?
I tend to get them here.
So I get them on my lower back.
It hurts the most.
It hurts.
You know... it's the smallest thing you can see.
My food life depends on it.
It hurts just to drink a little water.
Even if I eat something a little salty, it hurts.
I hate it.
If you chew it, you can get it.
Don't you? Tongue?
Not tongue.
Not just my tongue, but my cheeks.
I bite my cheeks a lot.
Then why can't you do it?
I don't know.
I bite a lot.
And then it hurts.
It hurts... in the moment.
But I've never had that white pig thing.
I've never had a white pig or anything like that.
Can you get it on your lips?
I mean, on your lips, you're probably getting herpes or something, right?
Yeah, that too.
I don't know why I don't have it.
Maybe you don't notice it. You don't notice it? You mean she's in a lot of pain? Is that it?
Are you that stoic? You want to do it, don't you? What? You're wasting your time! You know those patches that everyone wears?
Didn't they give them out around town for a while? I've never seen a corner empatch! Did you ever get one in Shibuya?
But you know, you don't meet people who want them, but you meet people who don't need them.
I want to use it, but I haven't used it yet. You know those corner empatches that come off when you eat a meal with them on?
You know, the Corner Empatch, the cream that numbs you a little bit?
Don't you know? You can eat anything with it. Wow.
That's great. Can you corner enchiladas? Can you do that? Can you do that if you don't have enough Gitabine?
What about the kids who take multivitamins? Oh, you're taking them? Is that what I think it is? Let's all take a multivitamin.
That's a weird promotion. I didn't know people could get it.
Is it just your body type or something? You mean like how you don't get pimples?
Or a happy environment? But my mom talks about her mouth a lot.
Oh, so it's genetic? Genetically, it's your father, isn't it? Some people say you don't get it as you get older.
Yeah, why? Why? Because she's got a really old mouth.
I don't know. I mean, what's wrong with your gums? Oh, but have you ever had a dentist tell you that your gums are weak?
Like, "Let's be careful. Like, are you not old enough to have a mouth? Like 5 or 60?
I'd like to find out. What? I don't like that. That would cause a lot of problems.
Low oral age, teeth and all. That's scary. What do you mean by "oral age"?
I've never heard of it.
So, that's how I'm fighting. That's why Maya had the surgery.
It was a while ago. I think it must have been incredibly painful. The body doesn't feel pain for a period of time.
Really? It's a period when they don't feel pain. So often, when you have a sore throat due to inflammation and a hoarse voice, it's because the inflammation is in a different place.
It's not a biological inflammation. It is not an inflammation of the organism. That was certainly the case with me. I didn't have a sore throat.
That's right. I thought I had a sore throat. What is this hospital conversation?
That's it. All adults drink alcohol, go to karaoke, and the next day their voice is dead.
That is because they sang while their bodies were swollen from drinking alcohol.
That is why I heard that people who think they are good at singing karaoke after drinking alcohol are different. That's not true. It's just that the organism is more likely to stick together.
Wow, doctor. What is this? Was it a trivia question? It was trivia talk.
I think it's number 5. Is it number 5?
What is it really called? It's the same with old age.
It depends on the age of the person. I'm sure there are many theories in the comments.
Because I've had it since I was a little girl. Some people have them. It's the same with acne. I think there are definitely people who get pimples easily and people who don't get pimples easily.
That's why.
Please take a multivitamin.
Click here to contact me. Seiya Yasumoto.
He will never appear in the lower grades. Too far away. That's true.
But they're all fighting on campus. That's true. Maybe they all go to places like Cocona.
Yes, they do. The older we get, the more we talk about health, don't we?
It's a very exciting topic, isn't it? What have you been doing lately? Health.
Nonakamaru said we talk about health all the time. Nonaka?
Isn't that what we're talking about? Health. It's still a school talk.
I've thought a lot about dental health. I know a lot about beauty.
I know a lot about teeth. Brushing my teeth twice a day is the best.
There is also an appropriate number of times to brush your teeth. I heard that many people overdo it.
Too much is not good. Because, you know, there were people who participated yesterday.
We were shooting a music video. In such a case, you know, after eating a little bit, brush your teeth, and after eating a little bit, brush your teeth five times a day.
You brush your teeth about five times a day. That is a way to lower the age of your teeth.
Not to raise, but to lower? It doesn't raise your age, it lowers it. Does it make me younger?
Does it increase the age of your teeth? Teeth going up? You heard about the over grinding?
The more you brush, the more you lose the coating, so two times is really good.
So, two times is really good. Brush when you wake up in the morning and before you go to bed at night. That's why I'm doing it right.
It's like washing your face too much, right? That's the idea. If you remove too much sebum, you get acne.
They say that the barrier function decreases, so I thought that the barrier is important.
So, by brushing twice, does Yasumoto-san prevent pimples from forming in the mouth as well? It's possible.
And the sparkle of his teeth. Yasumoto's teeth!
Teeth! Teeth! Teeth! Teeth! Teeth! Don't stop at the teeth!
You know that thing about washing your body? This is also connected to the barrier, but I don't use body soap these days.
You've been doing this for two months? Wait! Have you heard of this? The caloric acid formula. What does that mean? They don't use body soap.
I don't wash my body. Usually. It sounds dirty, doesn't it?
But a human being... Wait a minute! I'm so glad I cracked this open!
Aya, you're so 3D, I have to take it! Why are you talking like this?Aya, you're too 3D, you have to take it! Why are you talking like this?
You're so multi-talented.
If people take a bath every day at 38 degrees, that's all it takes to get rid of dirt. The power of the hot water.
That's why we don't need body soap. In the summer, it is important to use a body soap to compensate for the smell of feet and the oil and grease they produce, but in the winter, just using hot water is enough. It's dry, isn't it?
It's fine. My teeth feel better that way. Lately, when people touch my arms, they say they feel smooth and silky.
That's because I don't use body soap.
I've been getting more and more compliments on my body lately, especially when all I do is put on body cream like everyone else.
You sure are smooth, Aya. It's not dry anymore.
I don't scrub anymore. I don't scrub anymore.
On the contrary, I soften my skin with hot water and take a shower afterwards. Aya, I don't think you can have a boyfriend.
Is it because I'm a floral person that it's working? Is that what you mean?
That kind of person produces too much sebum, right?
That's why it's important to know if it's right for their body or not, right?
Yes, yes, yes. Speaking of washing, does anyone else suffer from back acne?
This is the latest. It just keeps popping up.
If you're suffering from back acne, I hope you're lying and wash with Muse medicated soap.
It's a common standard. They say you have to wash your hands.
It is said that lathering up with Muse medicated soap can properly sterilize the skin, and after all, back pimples are often easy to form because they get wet when sleeping.
So, some people are concerned about it in the summer, but I really want them to try it because I think it's a lie.
If you put lotion on your back like this, it will be cured.
Does that mean I don't need to lather? Do you mean I should just go straight on without lathering?
I think it's better to lather up. As for muse, I think it's better to lather up.
It's too strong. It's better to wash it with a soft foamy lather.
I see.
That's great. A lot of things are coming out.
I got a lot of stuff.
Is there anything you can think of? I've been thinking about it a lot, but I don't have anything.
But you've been talking about Pilates lately. Maya's Pilates is very interesting.
She told me last month that she joined Pilates because she started this month.
So I can go four times a month, right? I can go to Pilates four times a month. I can go four times a month.
And I can carry over one time.
So I heard that about halfway through the month of February.
And Maya thought it was four times including the trial. I said, "Of course not.
February was a month with a lot of expeditions. I was away a lot in Tokyo. I was not in Tokyo a lot.
So, February is only 28 days long.
I was hardly in Tokyo from the beginning of February, and I went to Tokyo three times in the last week of the year.
So I don't understand. I mean, he says he does Pilates after the lessons.
I'm overworking. Overworking.
I don't know if my body is getting healthier or not, but I don't like it, so I haven't been able to go once in March.
I haven't felt the most benefit from Pilates.
It's so much fun. I've never been to a place where appearance counts.
You can't go to a place like that. Maybe.
That's right. I'm right.
That's why I'm trying Pilates now, so I only have... 15 more days in March?
Isn't that too much? It's about time.
Yeah, it is. It's not good. It's going to happen all over again.
It's true. My body regularly at least once a week.
I wanted to strip my hair once a week.
It's not easy, you know, I'm not handsome.
Indeed.
I do pilates to catch up.
It's hard to incorporate that kind of thing into my daily routine.
I guess so.
Go to the next corner.
I won't stop. I'm not stopping now.
But it was good. This was probably more intense than this one.
I guess it's a thick story, right? I'm just sharing trivia, so there are many theories.
There are many theories.
You have to do what's right for your body.
Please do it.
Yes, I do. So, that's all for now, because it was a pleasant, funny, and stable talk.
It was a pleasant and fufufufu talk about health.
Today is March 14, so we are going to continue with this project.
It's called "Hilarious White Day.
I'm waiting.
We are waiting.
We three are the girls who want to get a present for White Day.
We are waiting for you, the viewers, to send us gifts that we would like to receive on White Day.
It's a comment, so you can write anything you want.
We will choose one person from each member who sent us a comment that he/she would like to receive this.
We will return the message with lots of love right here.
So, I have a little something to say about this, too.
What? What? What?
The bangs.
Bangs.
What is it? What's wrong?
I've heard about this.
Yes, yes, yes.
Mayo said she saw it on TV.
You were saying that you saw a TV program on White Day that ranked the most popular gifts that women want to receive for White Day.
What was that show the other day?
Um...
Nino-san.
Nino-san. It was at noon.
It was Nino-san at noon.
NTV.
And I was watching it.
And I thought that most of them were chocolate.
Hmmm.
And then I heard about chocolate and sweets.
I heard that it was sweets.
That's something.
Yes, that's what it was.
It's pretty low down on the line.
That's right.
You were about 8th, right?
What? I was like, "What?
The candy bars.
Yeah.Yeah.
And what a necklace in first place.
Yeah.
Second place went to travel.
Travel?
Why that?
It's about 10,000 yen at the most.
That's right.
Because chocolate is expensive.
I see.
So...
Chocolates aren't that expensive, right?
Yes, it is.
But you know what?
I don't think so.
That's it.
And the most expensive ones are around 10,000 yen.
That's right.
That's not true.
The return gift would be three or four times as much.
Well, okay.
I thought it was scary for a woman to receive 3 or 4 times as much at a low price.
That's true.
It's like, "You're asking for it, aren't you?
You're asking for it.
But you know what?
This is meaningful to me.
But, you know...
It depends on who you give it to, doesn't it?
Ah...
The survey was part of the show.
I don't think it was a "lovers" type of thing.
I don't think it was a "lovers" type of conversation.
It was more like they were asking for a gift in return from a coworker.
It was more like, "Women are scary.
But, for example, I gave chocolate to my girlfriend.
And she gave it back to you.
Don't you think "wow"?
Huh?
Heh.
I'd be like, "Oh, my.
I think I know more about chocolate than you do.
Well, I guess each of us has our own way of doing things.
If it were me...
I'm probably the type of girl who likes chocolate.
I'm the type of girl who goes to Salon du Chocolat.
That's true.
I like chocolate, don't you?
So I'd give her some chocolate.
It's delicious. It's good, but...
You know the type.
If you give me back some chocolate from a GoDie bar or something, I'll think.
I'd think, "No, I know and I can buy it.
Yes. Then I'll buy it here.
I'll buy it myself.
If you were to return something to Mayama-san, what would it be?
What would you give back to Mayama-san?
If I were to give it back to Mayama-san...
If you were going to give it back to me, I have something.
What?
This is good, isn't it?
How about a crab?
Crab?
That's a pretty good line, isn't it?
Crab is good, right?
I don't need food.
What?
I'm not that kind of guy.
I don't want food.
He said he's going to buy you a condo.
I don't want it.
That's not true.
I don't want it. I don't want something that big.
Oh, that's a tough one. Food is no good.
A ring.
I don't want it.
It's true, I don't want it the way you said it.
It's a ring, isn't it?
Dumbbells.
Mr. Tent-style will give it to you.
I don't want it!
So, let's set this up so that everyone is in love with me.
Let's do that.
I'm not your girlfriend.
We don't have time for this. Good for you.
Yes, it is.
I recommend this cartoon.
You've got good taste.
It's a gift with the recipient in mind.
I see.
This is tasteful.
I like it.
Do you want to take a look at it?
Think about Mayama.
Dinner on a date.
That's different.
I'm happy for you.
Think about Mayama.
A pair of tickets to Disney? What's this?Disney pair tickets? This is.
It's a pensicket.
It's a penny ticket. Pair tickets?
No?
No.
I give you Sue.
I'm giving away Sue.
What Sue?
Sue.
What's Sue?
I give you Sue. GarbageGomisoo. I give you Sue.
Good taste.
You don't see the pin down there? This.
It's Diane's story.
Diane Tsuda's "I give you Sue.
Garbage, garbage, garbage.
Hey, hey, hey. Don't let Mizusawa tell you.
I give you Sue.
I give this person MOTRANOV3Z Sue.
Thank you very much.
I'll take this.
Do I have to return this comment with a loving message?
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
I'm so relieved.
Let's go to many comedy gigs together.
Thank you very much.
Like that.
Okay, next.
I want to get one too. Valentine's Day.
You want a valentine?
You don't mind? No?
Aya gives you chocolate and you give her chocolate back. Do you like it?
Not at all. I'm happy.
It's like giving food for Valentine's Day.
What was I going to say about Valentine's Day?
You know how they say Valentine's Day is like a reverse Valentine's Day?
I have a dream of having someone do that for me.
I see.
That will come true on White Day, right?
That's right.
You're getting chocolate.
I'm happy.
Good.
Shall we go then, Aya?
For Aya.
What do you have for me? Gentlemen.
Presents.
I'm going to say anything.
What will you give me?
What's this?
A sauna.
Beauty products.
I'm so happy, happy, happy.
Please stop by the person who thought it was good.
This is difficult.
I'll give you 1 million yen for DTM equipment.
I'm happy, I'm happy, I'm happy.
You're happy about all of it.
It'll lead to work.
Isn't this so nice?
My brother can't cook, but he was making chocolates at midnight.
That's so cool.
Give me some of those, bro.
I'm a little scared of reverse chocolates from someone who can't cook.
I wonder what's in them.
The feeling.
He's giving me a fancy toothbrush.
I'm happy, happy.
I'm particular about my teeth.
It's all good.
I'll write you a letter.
I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy, I'm so happy.
I'm happy, I'm happy, I'm happy, I'm happy, I'm happy, I'm happy, I'm happy...
Wait, are you trying to make me feel better? Are you trying to up the ante?
Are you trying to up the ante? I'm trying to get it up.
I'm happy about everything. Oh, is that what this is?
Yeah, everything's bad, because you're a cheapskate, so you're happy with anything you get.
How about an original song, since you won't buy it yourself?
I'll think about it.
I'll use it as a study material.
You just made a great face. In the middle.
He had a look on his face that said he definitely didn't want it.
A ballpoint pen that's so easy to write with.
I'm totally happy with that, but I don't know what to do.
Isn't it difficult? Deciding.
Maybe he's looking at me like I'm looking at him. Maybe I don't want it.
You don't want it? It's fun.
I don't have to do it more than once.
I think it's time you made up your mind.
I don't know. I don't care what it is.
Anything is fine, guys.
What should I do? I think I'll get some eye contact from you.
I'll write down 100 things I like about Aya and send it to you.
That's fine.
You can write anything you want.
You can write them.
On the contrary, I'm starting to get letters saying, "Don't you need anything? I'm starting to get "Maybe you don't need anything?On the contrary, they are starting to write, "Don't you need anything? I'm starting to get a lot of "don't you need anything?
The only one that looks at it from my point of view.
I thought it was the only one, but it's funny.
It's funny.
I thought it was funny.
Aya, you're looking at it from my point of view, too.
Please give a message to the person who sent it to you.
I'm not interested in "looking at it from this side," but I'd like to read it together and like "looking at it from this side" with you. Thank you.
I'm not too good at comments like this.
I know, I know.
I get embarrassed by them.
The last one is Hime.
What?
Hime is happy when I give her chocolate.
If it's good chocolate, she's very happy.
That's the highest hurdle.
It's so delicious.
It's the highest hurdle.
Because you don't know what the deliciousness of the future is.
There are people who are aware of it. This project is a great pleasure. That's right.
Bingo.
It's a little more than realistic, what?
It's good to be out of the box.
I like the out-of-the-ordinary ones.
So, please, everyone, give it to Hime.
Please give it to Hime.
Yoshida goal!
Goal!
Confidence.
We often do that when we're filming, don't we?
Goal!
Our Kobayashi's signature pose is Yoshida Goal, so we are using it.
Goal, please write about it, too.
I'm writing something for Mire-chan right now.
Goal, please write.
I am writing a present for White Day.
I also want a stage for Mork. I can't do Mork at night.
A list of parks where you can do it at night.
A year's supply of multivitabies.
That's nice. I can't do parks.
But can you afford it?
A piece of wood.
I don't want it.
Cacao seeds.
If you give me all the families that will grow them and turn them into chocolate, fine.
Good at begging.
Certainly.
Muse for a month.
Muse now okay. I don't want it.
I'll rent out Disney.
That's a good idea.
You know what? Disney.
That's not what I'm talking about.
No, it's not.
Wrap it up. Roll it up.
Shacho-san is teaching.
Nakamoto's stadium.
I want it most.
I've decided.
You've decided?
I want to give my family to An.
Nakamoto's stadium.
I have to accumulate more than 300 points for Nakamoto's stadium.
It's a lot of work.
I'm almost there and I'm going to get Nakamoto's long T-shirt.
That's great, too.
The stadium is too high a hurdle.
I would love to have it as soon as you give it to me.
Thank you very much.
Let's eat a lot of Nakamoto.
Is it the ending? Isn't it early?
Sooner the better.
Thank you all for writing so many presents.
That's all for now, a merry and happy White Day.
I wonder what happened to Mr. Goh?
Mr. Goh, you didn't give a comment after all.
I didn't get it, did I?
So, the 55th edition of Ebichu's Delightful Showroom has come to an end in no time at all.
Here are many announcements from Ebichu.
It's White Day to all of you.
First of all, the 14th single.
It's been 4 years since its release.
How about today? will be released on May 3.
There will be a first edition, a regular edition, and a fan club limited edition with solo jackets of each member.
So there are a lot of forms.
Free live concerts will be announced and so on.
There are a lot of things planned until May, so please look forward to it.
And we are going to hold "Ebi City Junior High School Spring Tour 2023 100% EBISM Spring Tour".
General sales will start this Saturday, March 18, at 10:00 a.m.
This tour will run from April 15 to April 16.
We will do our best!
We will be touring all over Japan for about 3 months, so please come and visit us at a venue near you.
We are also open to vocal performances, so there may be some changes depending on the situation, but for now we are OK, so please look forward to seeing us.
We will also have the Setouchi Idol Festival on March 26, 2023, and next week and the week after that.
There will be two stages.
The set list is already well prepared, so please come and dance with us. Please come and dance with us.
And also, the live Blu-ray will be on sale.
The live Blu-ray of "Kashiwagi Hyuga's Graduation Ceremony & New Style University Arts & Entertainment" will be released on March 29th, Hyuga's birthday.The live Blu-ray of Hyuga Kashiwagi's Graduation Ceremony & New Style University Performing Arts Festival will be released on Hyuga's birthday, March 29th.
The Blu-ray is also a huge volume and contains all 9 EBICHU members and 10 EBICHU members.
I hope everyone, whether you came to the live or not, will have a chance to see it. I hope you will enjoy it, whether you came to the live or not.
And there are many other things. I have a lot of things to talk about, but Mirei-chan is just an aside.
Mirei-chan is going to be on the air tomorrow. This is an aside, but it will be broadcast by Asahi Broadcasting Corporation.
U-KNOW will have "Super Invincible Class" on March 19 and "Sorokon" on the following day, which will also be distributed.
If you couldn't get tickets, please watch them.
And on March 21, there will be a welcome debut for TVK's 50th anniversary event.
Kamune, who has been a great help to us, will be graduating, and we hope you will be there to witness it.
As announced yesterday, I will be releasing a photo book.
It is a photo book of Okinawa. It is in the shrimp tour.
Clay Fun Sas of Okinawa Shisa will be released on April 3.
It will be released on April 3. It's fun.
Yes, that's right.
I hope you will pay attention to Ebitu-chan from spring.
We really have a lot of announcements.
I'm grateful for that.
So many announcements.
Please pay attention.
Do you want to announce the final ranking?
Here are the final rankings.
Fifth place, Mr. Shackelford. Thank you very much.
In fourth place, Ric...
Peach shrimp.
Peach shrimp. You've changed, now.
Fifth place, Riku. Congratulations!
4th place, Mr. Momoebi Haraichi. Thank you very much.
Third place, Mr. Ooya. Thank you very much.
2nd place, Mr. GO. Thank you very much.
In first place, Mr. Zeroro. Zero-Ro Seven. Thank you very much.
Okay, so the next pleasant and happy showroom will be on April 5 at 7:00 p.m.
April 5th, 7:00 p.m.
It will be on April 5 at 7:00 p.m. Thank you very much.
Too many announcements and the days are getting longer and longer.
Thank you.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Then I would like to do a takopan the month after that.
Please look forward to it.
Thank you very much.
This delivery will also include the review meeting that will take place after this.
Oh, no.
None. No review session.
I talked too much.
Not enough time, not enough time.
Not enough scale.
Not enough scale, so I hope we can do it again with these members by all means.
Thank you very much for the fun time we had today.
That's all for now.
CJB was the main actor.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching.